good afternoon good afternoon I am from Ukraine, the
добрый день Добрый день Я из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky And you are
город Хмельницкий А вы
from the Moscow region I am from Russia, a city Which city
Я из Подмосковья Я из России город Какой
of the Moscow region is
из Подмосковья
Klin Klin I don’t know Khimki I know
город Клин Клин не знаю Химки знаю
Pushkin I know Serpukhov I know Klin I don’t know the new one I
Пушкина знаю Серпухов знаю Клин не знаю
learned
новый выучил
Klin the most ass there Tver region
Клин самый жопе там Тверская область
This is not according to the map like south yes  it turns out
Это не по карте типа южнее да получается
No, this is the
Нет это
Leningrad Highway
Ленинградское шоссе
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
from my Klin, so Sitting in a wedge, how do you feel
из своего Клина так Сидя в клини вы как
about you, not in Ukraine, support
относитесь к вы не в Украине поддержите
, firstly, I will correct it, secondly, not in a wedge,
во первых поправлю во вторых не в клине
but in Klin
а в Клину
together, secondly, of course, I consider
вместе во вторых конечно же я считаю
myself an adequate person, I do not
себя адекватным человеком я не
support the war, I
поддерживаю войну я не поддерживаю
I don’t support Putin I don’t support Putin’s policy
Путина я не поддерживаю политику Путина
I think that the Russian
Я считаю то что российской
state is a fascist
государственное это фашистское
state, it’s complete fascism and I
государство это сплошной фашизм и мне
absolutely don’t feel sorry for these [ __ ] orcs
абсолютно не жалко этих ебучих орков
who go to a foreign country to
которые едут в чужую страну устраивать
arrange some other people’s laws there Therefore, so that
там чужие какие-то законы Поэтому чтобы
your Hammers grind all these
ваши хаммерсы перемололи всех этих
bastards For me  these are not Russians, this is a
ублюдков Для меня это не россияне это
negative gene pool, for example, they
отрицательный генофонд например сейчас
immediately announced mobilization if I take you,
же мобилизацию объявили если Вас
for example  that I will, I will run to the
например возьмут что я буду я буду до
last, run away, renounce, and
последнего бегать убегать отрекаться и
so on, I will not allow
так далее я не позволю
my soul to kill someone and in general, in
своей душе убить кого-то и вообще в
principle, be killed That is, I will
принципе быть убитым То есть я грех на
not take sin upon myself Well, if only because
себя не возьму Ну хотя бы потому то
you understand that mobilization to
чтобы понимаете то что мобилизация для
protect the country  this is one
защиты страны это одно
murder of our Fraternal Ukraine this is
убийства нашей Братской Украины это
another
другое
I no longer think that in Ukraine we consider
Я уже не думаю что в Украине мы считаем
now Even those who considered Fraternal
теперь Даже те кто считали Братской
say, but nevertheless I will
говорят но тем не менее я буду
assert my opinion I hope that
утверждать свое мнение Я надеюсь что
in 50-100 years something may
через лет 50-100 может быть что-то
change because we  we
поменяется потому что нас корни все
still have roots, we have mixed blood, and
равно есть у нас есть смешанные крови и
so on, maybe something will change. I
так далее может быть что-то поменяется Я
apologize to all Ukrainians
прошу прощения у всех украинцев
for their Russian Javanese cattle. The people who
за свой русский [__] явский Народ у
have no brains and who cannot
которых нету мозгов и которые не могут
think adequately and objectively, the whole
мыслить адекватно и объективно вся весь
world has turned its back on Russia, and this  the redneck
мир отвернулся от России а это [__]
population still continues to [ __ ]
население до сих пор продолжает [__]
walk the letters Z [ __ ] on their forehead so that they
ходить буквы Z нахуй на лбу чтобы они
die like this you look at the elections
сдохли вот так вот смотрите вы на выборы
go interesting
ходите интересно
used to go now it makes no sense to go for
раньше ходил сейчас нет смысла ходили за
whom you voted  In what year did they
кого голосовал В каком году из этого
vote
голосовали
?
Ой я ходил последний раз год назад Когда
Russia against Putin against this
России против Путина против данного
regime, please Anyone except Putin Well,
режима пожалуйста Любой кроме Путина Ну
to show some kind of alternative Yes, to
чтобы показать какой-то альтернативу Да
show an alternative, but there was absolutely no difference,
показать альтернативу но разницу никакой
one gang turned out to be absolutely
получилась одна банда абсолютно
But look at you now,
А вот смотрите у вас сейчас
I heard that there were not numerous people who went out there in Moscow
я слышал что выходили там в Москве не
that now people are afraid for
многочисленные что сейчас люди боятся
even more than a month  back
еще больше чем месяц назад
but I watch that the video is from poor regions
но я смотрю что видео с бедных регионов
And their wives are taken away there the mainland
И забирают жены ихние там материк
screams but everyone is silent everyone everyone is silent they are
кричатся но все молчат все все молчат
indignant but no one accepts
возмущаются но никто не принимает
some reluctantly not in Dagestan they
каких-то нехотя не вот в Дагестане там
blocked the road there it was what yours
перекрыли дорогу было вот с чем вашим
is connected with people understand that their husbands
это связано люди понимают что их мужей
children are taken away to be slaughtered and, as it were, they just
детей увозят на убой и как бы просто
cry, but do nothing.
плачут но ничего не делает Почему так
Why is that
Смотрите дело в том то что как
?  The Indian people are a free people, and
украинский народ это свободный Народ а
Russia is slaves, they are terpils, they will
Россия это рабы это терпилы они будут
endure until the last [ __ ] until they are
терпеть до последнего пока [__] пока их
simply covered with nuclear weapons,
просто ядерным оружием не накроет
I didn’t tolerate Why are you part of
я не терпила А почему вы что же часть
this people, why then there are terpils,
этого народа почему тогда есть терпилы
there are not terpils Here’s how to increase the
есть не терпила Вот как увеличить
number of tinkers
количество нетерпил
Look at the case  the fact that the amount of the
Смотрите дело в том то что количество
mass suppresses the minority the minority,
массы подавляет меньшинство меньшинство
that is, people like me 15-20 percent 15
то есть таких как я 15-20 процентов 15
20 already Shock Such a revolutionary force is
20 уже Ударная Такая сила Революционная
also very small
тоже это очень мало
if you look at any changes in society by
если смотреть любые изменения в обществе
children 15 20 percent there is about 5-10
детьми 15 20 процентов там порядка 5-10
That is, 15-20 is  20 percent, every
То есть 15-20 это 20 процентов каждый
fifth person, you
пятый человек это у вас на лестничной
should have two people like you on the landing.
площадке должно быть двое Таких как вы
Besides the fact that it is 15 percent
Помимо того то что это 15 процентов
against Putin’s policy, these 15
против путинской политики эти 15
percent will still sit at home,
процентов все равно будут сидеть дома
damn it, the last [ __ ], they will
[__] да последнего нахуй Вот будут
sit and sit, sit and sit, I’m already
сидеть и сидеть сидеть и сидеть я уже
[ __ ]  it’s just
заебался терпеть у меня уже просто в
getting burned in one place I don’t know what the
одном месте подгорает Я не знаю чего
Russians are waiting for what they want,
русские ждут чего они хотят
it’s just that you say there what they are waiting for  t
просто вот вы говорите там чего они ждут
But what are you waiting for Here you are
А вот Чего вы ждете Вот вы 7 месяцев
also watching this for 7 months and think what they
тоже наблюдаете это и думаете чего они
are waiting for So how do you manifest yourself then how
ждут Так а как вы тогда проявляетесь как
do you move forward Let's say this is a
вы двигаете вперед Вот это скажем
change
изменение
I just decided for myself what to go out
Я просто решил для себя то что выходить
with a poster No war or there is just
с плакатом Нет войне или там просто
an empty piece of paper when  I will be raked into a
пустым листочком когда меня загребут в
pre-trial detention center or an isolation ward There, and so on, it
СИЗО или изолятор Там и так далее в этом
doesn’t make sense, I’m just rowed
нет в этом нет смысла меня просто гребут
and I won’t be able to fight, I decided to somehow
и всё я не смогу бороться я решил как-то
inspire people there at my work with the
внушать там на своей работе людям
right position so that they start
правильную позицию чтобы они начали
thinking, I’ll probably soon [ __ ] my father
думать я уже наверное скоро своему отцу
I’ll break him [ __ ] me [ __ ] him
[__] разобью Он меня [__] нахуй он
today I came to him he came out to me
сегодня я к нему приехал он вышел ко мне
in Putin’s huskies Well I don’t know my
в путинской лайки Ну я не знаю у меня
mother, thank God from my mother, she has
мамка слава Богу от мать у меня
seen the light she’s transferred to our side with her brother
прозрела она пере на нашу с братом
she already understands that now the
сторону она уже понимает то что сейчас
children will be called now what now
детей призовут сейчас что сейчас
what is happening She that she started she started
происходит Она что она начала она начала
digging on the Internet this is the most important
копаться в интернете это самое главное
thing my
батя у меня [__] Он до сих пор
dad is a dumbass He still watches Skobeev and Solovyov and that's the
смотрит скабееву и Соловьева и вот что
most important thing we have total propaganda
самое главное у нас тотальная пропаганда
because of propaganda, the Russian people
из-за пропаганды русский народ и [__]
will die and [ __ ] die, damn Well, look The
подохнет погибнет [__] Ну смотри Дело в
fact is that Propaganda I also often
том что вот Пропаганда Я тоже часто
thought Propaganda and I tend to think
думал Пропаганду и склоняюсь к мнению
many people Correctly say that
многие люди Правильно говорят что
Propaganda works when
Пропаганда она действует тогда когда
there is ground for this propaganda,
есть почва для этой пропаганды вот
for example, it didn’t fall on you  Propaganda
например на тебя же не легла Пропаганда
fell on my father somewhere. Here he grew up somewhere in a
где-то на отца легла Вот он где-то в
scoop, so he has this
совке вырос так у него есть вот это
basis and on this soviet Basis it is
базисовку и на этот совковой Базис это
Propaganda.
Пропаганда легла
If you now do Propaganda,
Если ты сейчас будешь делать Пропаганду
for example,
например
cutting off your ears
отрезание себе ушей
There is Ukraine because people who have
Украину есть потому что люди у которых
it somewhere. She has been sitting for years that, like, yes,
где-то Вот она сидела годами что вот да
like, we should give America back to Ukraine
типа мы должны Америке надавать Украине
to return the Union, the Empire, all [ __ ].
вернуть Союз Империю всякая фигня
Look, the fact is that there are a
Вот смотри Дело в том что вот есть очень
lot of people like you who
много людей таких как ты так который
have a clear position against
имеет четкую позицию против
they don’t come out  on the street because they see that
не выходят на улицу потому что видят что
it's pointless. So far, that is, they
это бессмысленно Пока так то есть они
want the police. But their not some kind of action is
хотят полиции Но их не какое-то действие
limited there by talking to the
ограничивается там по разговаривать с
relatives and with people at work, yes,
родственниками и с людьми на работе да
that’s cool too, because if you
это тоже круто Потому что если вы
change at least two people, this is already a
Измените хотя бы двух людей это уже
huge number,
огромное количество
but
но
it seems to me that you need
мне кажется что надо такие вещи
to expand some kind of Telegram channel there
расширять какие-то там Telegram канал в
within a reasonable framework in order
рамках разумного рамках того чтобы там
not to be substituted for any  it’s not
не подставляться под какие-то там не
necessary there and if you sit and say they can
надо там и если вы сидите и скажем могут
come knock you don’t have to write
вам прийти постучать не надо там писать
everything there to everyone On the assault on the winter like Lenin
там все всем На штурм зимнего как Ленина
Wiki Yes, but you need to convey some thoughts you
Вики Да но нужно доносить мысли какие-то
can do it there in some say the
можно это делать там в каком-то скажем
right key such that it’s safe
правильном ключе такому что безопасно
for example  publish
например публиковать в Telegram канале
some discussions of the
какие-то обсуждения
briefing of the Ministry of Defense on the Telegram channel Yes, if they are already
брифинга Минобороны Да если там вот уже
saying that they shot down 100
они говорят что сбили там 100
Ukrainian aircraft there, in total there were 50 before they
украинский самолета всего там 50 было до
said
заявляли
or as they say that yes, the losses of the Russian
или как говорят что да потери российской
army are only 5937 people there yes yes
армии всего лишь там 5937 человек да да
, 300 thousand are needed for mobilization
на мобилизацию нужно 300 тысяч
everything is fine with us, we only have six
У нас все хорошо у нас только там шесть
thousand people there, we have an army of a million there
тысяч человек у нас армия миллион там
or two million we brought to Ukraine.
или два миллиона мы завели в Украину Там
Only a limited contingent
всего лишь ограниченный контингентом
died there  6
погибло 6
we urgently need
нам нужно срочно
[music] a
[музыка]
person who can reason at least a little bit
человек который может хоть немножко
compare figures
рассуждать сопоставлять цифры
you have some kind of things like that
вас есть какие-то там такие вещи
on the street Yes they issue subpoenas at the
на улице Да выдают повестки у станции
metro station
метро стоят
Well in Moscow of course the metro is only in
Ну в Москве конечно метро только в
Moscow in St. Petersburg
Москве в Питере
Yekaterinburg I live in Klin we
Екатеринбурге Я живу в Клину у нас
go  but I don’t open it I’m waiting for me to go to
ходят но я не открывай Я жду мне на
work they should bring me I work in a
работу должны принести Я работаю в
state institution so I’m waiting There
государственном учреждении вот я жду Там
if they bring me straight from work
если мне принесут я прям [__] с работы
I’ll run away from work I already don’t give a [ __ ] I already
побегу мне уже похуй я уже я уже для
decided for myself that today I’m some kind of
себя решил то что я сегодня какой-то
post there is something  which one I threw there I was driving
пост там кое-какой закинул там я ехал
today from work and in front of me was a
сегодня с работы и передо мной ехала
truck full of Grant’s white frets
фура вся забитая белыми ладами Гранта
Yes, I took a picture and put it up and the fact that they say
Да я сфоткал и выставил и то что мол
[ __ ] gifts for Russians are being brought [ __ ]
[__] подарочки для русских везут нахуй
So that people just a little bit my mother
Вот чтобы люди чуть-чуть это мне мама
called me to sit
позвонила сидеть
zaebala everything just already has no strength  Well, I don’t have the
заебало все просто уже нету сил Ну нету
strength Well, it’s just that if such an opinion was at
сил Ну просто если бы такого мнения хотя
least 50 to 50, at least 50 would be different
бы 50 на 50 хотя бы 50 был по-другому
, they were in the rating two days ago
вот два дня назад были в рейтинге
But it’s putting it mildly for you, it’s generally
Но это мягко сказать для вас это вообще
a laugh I watched how it’s real in Ukraine
это смех Я смотрел как в Украине вот
oh free people how they arrange
реально вольные люди как устраивают
rallies And for us a person is taken away everyone is
митинги И для нас человека забирают все
[ __ ] filming a [ __ ] video But this is [ __ ] up Guys
видео [__] снимает Но это [__] Ребята
fighting back you understand that I live in a
отбиваетесь вы понимаете то что я живу в
small town we don’t have rallies
маленьком городе у нас митингов не
but small cities and we don’t need
проходит но маленькие города и не нужны
all the revolutions [ __ ] happen in big
все революции происходит [__] в больших
cities absolutely  that is, Moscow should
городах абсолютно то есть Москва должна
just stand up [ __ ] everyone is afraid everyone is
просто встать нахуй все боятся все
afraid for their own
боятся за свои
now they are afraid but now they
они сейчас боятся боятся но сейчас
will start to pull it out like this to catch it
начнут вот так вытягивать вылавливать
now it will start to reach little by little it wo
сейчас она начнет понемножку доходить
n’t be able to sit it out
уже отсидеться не получится
already [ __ ] handed out agendas to everyone I’m
уже [__] раздали всем повестки я вот я
sitting and waiting for the damn agenda to be brought to
сижу и жду когда мне [__] принесут
me I  I will not open I will
повестку я не буду открывать я буду
run I will run to the last to run I
бегать я до последнего чтобы бегать я не
will not take the sin on myself to kill someone
буду брать грех на себя убивать кого-то
or be killed I have a
или быть убит У меня есть дочь мне это
daughter  things, firstly, that they
несколько вещей во-первых то что из
made artificial cattle out of Russians, that
русских сделали искусственное [__] то
is, real Russian is cattle, that is,
есть реально русский это [__] то есть
80 percent of Russians are just cattle
80 процентов русских это просто быдлосы
to  who are not educated who do not have the
которые не образованы у которых нет
Internet which I can get
интернета который мне откуда черпать
information from I don’t think it seems to me
информацию Мне кажется не Мне кажется
people who have the Internet they
люди те у которых есть Интернет они
start to get information but they climb
начинают черпать информацию но они лезут
there what
туда что
corresponds to their worldview it’s not in the
соответствует их мировоззрению тут не в
absence of the Internet if you give a
отсутствии интернета если ты даешь
smart person the Internet
умному человеку интернет
where the programmer about programming
куда запрограммист про программирование
And if a person
А если человек
is not intellectually burdened by anything, he is
интеллектуально ничем не обременю он
looking for something that corresponds to his level of
ищету то что соответствует его уровню
development, the level of understanding of the world, I
развития уровнем понимания мира я
absolutely agree with you, it’s more convenient for everyone to
абсолютно с вами согласен всем удобнее
lie on the couch and watch the War, how the
лежать на диванчике и смотреть Войну как
hell
[__]
do you know, some part of the mobilization was announced with us A
Вы знаете мобилизация объявили у нас
small percentage began to
какая-то часть Малый процент начали
erase these letters Z
стирать эти буквы Z
when I spoke with the Russians I see that
когда общался вот русскими Я смотрю что
they perceive this war as you know,
они воспринимают эту войну как знаете
here we play football, ours scored there, yours
вот футбол играем наши там забили ваши
scored And now it turns out they understand
забили А сейчас Получается они понимают
that they are being pulled on the field to play
что их тянут на поле играть
[laugh]
[смех]
absolutely me, that's why I used to, well, no offense,
абсолютно я поэтому я раньше ну без обид
I treated them differently in Ukraine
я Украи к ним относился не так
loyal as it is now, now I'm just
лояльно как сейчас сейчас же я просто
proud of the Ukrainians, it's real  the free
горжусь украинцами это реально вольный
people are well done I'm just [ __ ] in
народ это Молодцы Я просто [__] Я в
shock I began to listen to Ukrainian songs and I
шоке я стал слушать украинские песни и я
'm on streams I apologize to the
ну на стримах Я извиняюсь перед
Ukrainians for my people you understand that
украинцами за свой народ вы понимаете то
it is very difficult for any person
что очень сложно для любого человека
to admit guilt admit weakness That is,
признать вину признать слабость То есть
it is necessary to show strength to show
это нужно чтобы проявить силу показать
that I  after all, the strong one needs to admit
что я все-таки сильный нужно признать
weakness, the Russians can’t do this. So
слабость русские этого не могут Вот вы
they start to come up with
они начинают придумывать
in order to justify Why
для того чтобы оправдать Почему они вот
they can’t say like this just damn yes
так они не могут сказать просто блин да
We crap like withdraw troops and
Мы обосрались типа вывести войска и
say now we will rake what
сказать сейчас будем разгребать то что
we are doing
мы делаем
these conversations here I am  how long it’s been there for
эти разговоры они вот я сколько уже там
7 months I’ve been communicating with the Russians,
7 месяцев получается общаюсь с русскими
I’m all in a non-logical,
я оно все лежит в плане не логическом
irrational plan, they understand everything,
каком-то иррациональном Вот они все
but he will find a thousand
понимают но он будет находить тысячу
reasons there from the fact that we shout at you, the
причин там от того что мы на вас кричите
chain brings out there you went to the Yanukovych rally, in
цепочку выводит там вы вышли на митинг
short, there you need to  everything is
Янукович короче там надо у них все это
so mixed up with them and you know
настолько перемешивается и вот знаешь
what is most interesting when they say
что самое интересное когда они говорят
that in this 8 years they bombed the Donbass And if
вот в этом 8 лет бомбили Донбасс И если
we  we look that last year 21 to
мы смотрим Что в прошлом году 21 до
something throughout the entire territory of the Donetsk
что-то на всей территории Донецкой
Lugansk region under the control of
Луганской области под контролем
Russian and Ukraine, about
российским и Украине погибло там порядка
20 or 30 years died there. Yes, and it’s not only
20 или 30 лет Да причём это не только
military operations that were blown up somewhere by mines
боевых действий где-то на минах
now it’s generally disproportionately people
сейчас это вообще несоизмеримо люди
came to protect
пришли защитить
there two  queues call names
там двое очереди обзываются
girlfriend Yes, somewhere there someone
подруга Да где-то там кто-то кого-то
pushed someone you run out with a gun to
толкнул ты выбегаешься автоматом чтобы
protect shot a bunch of people
защитить расстрелили кучу людей очереди
I don’t know orcs from your territory, you’re great, I don’t know, but damn, I just
вы молодцы я не знаю но [__] я прям
started to love Ukraine Let’s help You
стал любить Украину Давайте помогать Вы
move in the middle, too,
двигаетесь середины тоже немножко
stagger the movement a little more because you have to
шатайте сильнее движение потому что
wait Just for the Ukrainians to kick out like
ждать Просто чтобы украинцы выгнали типа
for you
за вас
Yes, they also tell me they tell me why
Да мне также говорят мне говорят почему
we should solve your problems
мы должны решать Ваши проблемы
Quite right  but when i'm one
Совершенно верно но когда вот я один
against 100 i can't do anything
против 100 я ничего не могу сделать Я
when i started i started running at work
когда началась я начал на работе
yat and there it turns out all
прогонять а там оказывается все
the morons frozen there are just [ __ ] Well,
замороженные там [__] одни [__] Ну
what can I do to make a
что я могу сделать
team so strong that you
команда настолько сильная то что вы
understand that the whole point is that you
понимаете то что все дело в том то что
can always find at least something there, you can
всегда можно найти хоть что-то там можно
draw pictures with some messages
рисовать картинки с какими-то месседжами
there, throw them into groups  VKontakte is still there,
там скидывать в группы ВКонтакте еще там
that is, you can always influence in some way,
то есть всегда можно влиять в каком-то
that is, you have to think just not to sit and
то есть надо думать просто не сидеть и
wait for the Ukrainians to drive away, like Russia,
ждать украинцы прогонят типа Россия
someone will decide for us.
кто-то за нас решит Никто за нас не
Well, when this is over Well,
[__] Ну когда это закончится Ну ну
okay, I won’t have any luck at all,
ладно не буду вообще удачи у вас всё
you will succeed, well done guys, good luck Come on,
получится вы молодцы ребята удачи Давай
people from Russia
люди из России
If you are against it before, understand that
Если вы против до этого поймите что
you can’t just sit out you won’t be able to
просто отсидеться вы не сможете вам
promise that there won’t be my situation 15 times
обещали что не будет мо ситуация 15 раз
before Peskov, they talked with Putin there  and
до Песков там с Путиным говорили а
now about and do it and it will continue to
теперь об и сделать и дальше еще будет
tighten the screws even more Therefore, yes, you
сильнее закручивать гайки Поэтому да не
can’t go to a rally there because you are the
можете там выйти на митинг потому что вы
only one in tomized, start
один в томизированные начинайте вести
propaganda on the Internet, start among
Пропаганду в интернете начинайте среди
of your
своих
compatriots Draw
соотечественников Рисуйте картинки
some pictures with instant messengers there Why
какие-то с мессенджерами там Зачем
fight there for Putin scatter on the
воевать там за Путина раскидывайте в
Internet there in Telegram channels in the
интернете там в Telegram каналах в
comments in a
комментариях в
contact somewhere else
контакте еще где-то
under the video Facebook
под видео Фейсбук
YouTube write show up do not
Ютубе пишите проявляйтесь не
preserve only there I am with
консервируйтесь только там я вот со
my relatives with my people
своими родственниками со своими людьми
at work  to expand that other people
на работе расширять что другие люди
saw that there are a lot of you Why Because
видели что вас много Почему Потому что
Everyone thinks around all the morons like for the
Каждый думает вокруг все [__] типа за
war But I'm the only one here No it's
войну А вот я тут один только Нет это
because you are silent When you start
потому что вы молчите Когда вы начнете
talking Yes write somewhere people
говорить Да писать где-то людей
will see Damn I'm not the only normal
будет видеть Блин я не один нормальный
one like that  not everyone around is a dumbass
такой так не все вокруг долбоебы
Change the words, there is more and people
Измените слова есть еще вот и у людей
begin to increase their confidence in themselves
начинает подниматься уверенность себе
further when the more there will be
дальше когда чем больше таких будет Да
Yes, these loyalists will look, they
вот эти лояльники будут смотреть они
usually
обычно
cheat when in Russian they lean to
схляется когда по-русски склоняются на
the other side the more and for the war, by and
ту сторону чем больше да и за войну
large, not so much  but they are
большому счету не так много но они вот
active aggressive And the main mass
активные агрессивные И основная Масса К
inclines to them, this mass will see that a
ним склоняет это масса будет видеть что
bunch of people behind m  ir Yes, there is against the war and the
куча людей За мир Да там против войны и
masses will very sharply begin to drift
масса очень резко начнет дрейфовать в
towards precisely this
сторону именно вот этого
anti-war to such a mood, so
антивоенного до такого настроения так
show up not just don’t have to wait
проявляйтесь не просто не надо ждать
until Ukraine does something there You
пока там что-то Украина сделает Вы
must bring closer You must bring closer the
должны приближать Вы должны приближать
vacillation of this regime because
шатание этого режима потому что В ваших
Ukraine is in your interests  Yes, Ukraine will expel
интересах Украина Да Украина выгонит
Russia, yes, but Russia, this
Россию да но Россия у вас вот это
will remain Putinism, you will have souls for nothing,
останется путинизм вас будут души даром
or do you think that after losing to
или вы думаете что после проигрыша
Ukraine in Russia, they will not tighten the
Украине в России не будет закручивать
screws even there Freedom of speech and so
гайки даже там Свобода слова и так
on, you didn’t even pick, Therefore, you
дальше вы даже не пикали Поэтому нужно
need to raise the right consciousness of your
нужно поднимать право сознание своих
fellow citizens and  to show that they will not be alone,
сограждать и показывать что они не одни
yes, it’s hard, it’s hard, it’s hard to
вы будете да это тяжело это тяжело надо
go through this stage in Ukraine, too, not
проходить этот этап в Украине тоже не
everything was like that at once people went to the Maidan
все так было сразу люди вышли на Майдан
before there were whole decades of political
до были целые десятилетия политической
struggle before there was a decade of all sorts of
борьбы до было десятилетие всяких там
rallies of protest movements, it’s
митингов движений протестных это все
not just Ukrainians woke up right away, we
не просто сразу украинцы проснулись мы
already such dates,
уже такие свидания
therefore, it is necessary to develop, wait until
поэтому надо надо развивать ждите пока
everyone around
все вокруг
wakes up d  o start waking them up it’s
проснуться до начинайте их будить
cool don’t wait until you wake up
прикольно не ждите пока проснуться
start to convince I love when such ideas are
начинать убедить люблю когда такие
invented on the go and topics
придумываются на ходу и темы
subscribe to the
подписывайтесь на канал
revir channel poking drink search Because often
revir тычие пить поиск Потому что часто
YouTube YouTube turned
YouTube YouTube включилась занимая
on by liking comments another channel robot of the soul the correct information on the right
души правильную информационно справа
can donate and shoes sky to have a bite
может донатом и обуви ского перекусить
to eat  kilo opus video
на килограмм опусе под видео